I ended up with plans to meet Yamada and borrow the next volume of that manga.
Why in Shibuya, though?
We could have just met at our local station.
And why did I get here so early?
It's not like I was excited or anything.
Just wanted to make sure I found the place.
Look, we're supposed to meet at two, right?
Is that...
really her?
Yep, that is definitely her.
You spooked me!
Were we meeting up at two?
Oh, yeah, um, I...
I just wanted to make sure we found the correct place is all.
Um, the manga...
So, hey!
There's this place that I want to check out.
You in?
I mean, I guess so.
Awesome!
Wow, she smells so nice.
Big crowd, huh?
Maybe because it's almost New Year's?
Let's go.
Uh...
More like because it's Christmas Eve.
帽色に 茜 射す日は柔らかにはぜた
沙涌に 僕らは目も開かぬまま
悲しくってしようがないんだ お日様で手が濡れた
眩しくって仕方がないし 途方に暮れた帰り
落ちてゆくように
茜が射したから もう少して
僕は僕をひとつは愛せたのに
車用に気づけば目もわかぬまま
雫のゆらぎの中
僕らは目もわかぬまま
Hmm. Yamada doesn't seem to have any idea what day it is. She's probably just here running
some other errands. Better try and not walk side by side, huh?
I look like a straight-up stalker!
That explains the look.
Huh? Oh! You finally showed your face!
This won't do at all. Here.
Oh, sorry. I'll carry it.
No?
We can't get split up this way.
Oh! You're gonna get in people's way! Stick close!
What am I, a dog?
Pancakes?
They look so nice, and I hear they taste great.
They're open for brunch.
Should we not?
No, we can.
This is bad.
This is starting to feel like a date.
Let's go!
Did you know? You shouldn't go to an amusement park on a first date.
Why not?
It gets awkward waiting in line, and the relationship ends up falling apart because of it.
But really, that doesn't seem true, does it?
Hmm?
What do you mean?
But now, what's bothering her?
Now that I think about it, I heard it's better if the guy stands in front on stairs and escalators.
I...
Huh?
I'll go in front.
No! Whoa! Don't get in front!
Why not? I...
And so then I'll say thank you.
I mean, we just...
What's the matter?
I...
Was just trying to figure out how you did your...
Hair.
My mom did it for me.
I can't really do something this intricate myself.
Really?
Yeah, why?
Nothing.
I just thought she seemed pretty strict when I saw her at our parent-teacher conferences.
She is when we're out.
But when we're at home, she's actually super chill.
She calls me Anna and everything.
That sounds pretty cute.
Huh?
Ichikawa.
I never heard you say cute.
Did I just creep her out?
Oh, wow!
I don't know what to pick!
Thank goodness she cheers up at Mach 10 speed.
Expensive!
What are you getting?
Just...
Just coffee.
What?
That's all?
I'm not big on...
Sweet stuff.
Aw.
Sorry.
I should have picked a regular cafe.
N-no.
It's okay.
Damn it all!
Are you ready to order?
We'll have the Berry Deluxe Pancake set with milk tea.
As well as...
Oh yes, a coffee.
Would you like that coffee hot or iced?
Which one?
Hot.
Hot, please.
House Blend or Cafe Americano?
Which one?
House Blend.
Blend, please.
Very good.
Just kill me now.
Ichikawa?
Huh?
You seem to really like black.
Oh yeah, my clothes.
Sure.
I don't own anything not black.
I like it too.
I'm not wearing any today.
But a lot of my clothes are actually black.
That's unexpected.
But I bet it looks a lot different on you than it does me.
Yeah?
Meaning?
When someone with nice fashion sense wears the color black, it always looks stylish and
real cool.
But for me, it's just the only color I don't avoid.
Wait, did I just start explaining fashion to a literal pro model?
Yeah, my stylist said the same thing to me.
Look at her struggle to follow that.
The things all look totally different depending on the person and their outfit.
This is bad.
I'm really racking up the mess up points quick today.
Sorry for the wait.
Here's our house blend.
I said I hate sweet stuff.
Wow.
It's like a bitter soup.
This was a poor choice.
I really shouldn't have come out here with her.
We get along fine at school and all, so I figured...
But out here, it's so much more obvious just what different lives we lead.
All right, here we are.
One berry deluxe pan headset.
Yum!
Look at this!
Wow!
Oh yeah, that's right.
I forgot.
Take a picture for me.
Oh, okay.
Right.
For the socials, of course.
I'm not eating it.
That's what this place is for.
She's going to share that face with the whole world.
But I mean, that's kind of a big bite.
How's that going to do on the socials?
Seriously?
I almost forgot.
She's still Yamada.
This would probably be better as a video.
Oh, that's a good idea!
And rolling.
Okay, let's cut.
Okay, director.
Wow!
I don't mind taking this, but are you sure you want to upload it?
Won't it look bad?
What?
No, I'm not posting this.
I'm sending them all to you.
Huh?
Don't forget the real thing.
Looky!
How's this?
looky how's this looks fine to me somehow I wound up tagging along on her
bubbly shopping trip what but I get paid for work and stuff I really messed up
back there at the cafe sorry must feel awkward
yeah I come with my sister sometimes oh yeah you two are close huh hey which
one do you think is cuter what I'd have no idea just buy whatever you want come
on I want to know which one you think is cuter huh well then this one this one
is cuter the colors more relaxed this is like a scene out of some rom-com on the
other side of this curtain Yama does I don't need to stand right in front you
do I've got something else to try on so wait right there don't get a boner
don't get a boner don't get up and wanting to get a new skirt
huh sounds good my sister and what do you think of this one huh it's my sister your
sister I should say hi not right now can I try this skirt on somewhere sure any of us
I'm sorry about this it's fine what's wrong nothing
hey about what you said about not right now why not when can I some other time when it's right
I promise then mm-hmm I was just trying this on but I sweated through it wait
aren't you gonna buy it why's that because it looks good on you
in that case maybe I'll buy it and wear it out
are you okay for time not like I have plans time sure is flying today hey sorry I know that you must be
exhausted getting dragged around so I'm sorry about that you know what us worried about today
all right I've been so preoccupied with myself that I didn't do much to put her mind at ease I guess
it's you know I you don't really know much about me huh I'm not a people person not someone afraid of
turning down invitations either when I want someone to screw off I say so when something sucks I say so
that's just the way I am so I guess that means today was fun I mean I guess it was
I can tell oh I mean you never talk about yourself like this I mean
have you always been that way no I just what's this for I wore it here this morning but then it got a
little too hot later I can't even look down anymore
I really wanted to come out and see this I've never seen this no way
okay that's a lie but I never knew the lights could be this nice
oh I'll carry the manga what's wrong nothing at all
the handles are pretty damp my hands get clammy
what if it's not this is a trap if I grab it again I'll be labeled a creep
sweaty hands
the Advisors
we're already done
the phone
the angry hands
holding both hers and your hands
the littleSomeone
the
gap
We've sort of lost sense of when to stop holding hands.
And just slowly, very slowly.
I'm worried. She might realize how I feel.
This is me, then.
Yeah. Have a happy new year.
There's still the 25th, 26th, 27th, 28th.
There's plenty left to go.
So, let's not say that.
Well, see ya.
Watch where you're going.
Ah!
Merry Christmas!
Ho! Ho ho ho!
The whole holy night thing...
Ho ho ho! Ho ho ho!
Doesn't really matter.
What are you doing?
I'm Yamada Santa!
Really?
But it almost feels like my feelings might get across.
Like she might know I like her.
I'm like, get close to her задачей.
Goodbye.
I'm always so happy.
I look so happy.
When I look at her, I just can see...
I have seen that.
But.
There's people from me...
I have seen that.
I've seen that.
Have seen me here.
Next time you.
作詞・作曲・編曲 初音ミク
初音ミク
I keep turning things over again in my head, thinking about all I should have done, the things I should have said. What was even with that whole day, though?
Are you... N-Nigorikawa?
I am you, and so you are me. Imaginary Kiyotaro.
I'm so obsessed, I've developed another personality.
Think about it, about what happened yesterday.
Not the pervy stuff. You said something rather important. Right there.
I said, not now.
You feel the power of it, don't you? Like you have a chance with her.
Well, I mean of course I do. We even held hands and all that. That's basically commitment.
But Yamada's always touchy-feely with her other friends, too. Maybe she's just treating me the same.
What do you think?
That could be.
Don't agree with me!
Why don't you try manning up and getting in shape? If she's still hanging all over you after that?
Well, you know what that means.
That means...
All these emotions are Yamada's fault, right?
Why do I always forget that?
When she's around.
Everything's fine.
Though...
You're there.
It all comes back to me.
See?
Eventually.
It's okay.
Okay.